>> Brian Holt: 现在当我们看到结果时，结果是好的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And now when we
look at results, results was fine,
SearchParams 现在很高兴，你可以看到它是绿色的。
SearchParams is now happy,
you can see that one's outlined in green.
现在，这是其中最困难的一个。
And now,
this is the most difficult one of them.
我们会说 App.js ，我们会把它重命名为 tsx 。
So we're gonna say App.js,
we're gonna rename it to tsx here.
别介意我开玩笑的
And never mind, I'm just kidding.
它只是在工作
It's, it just works.
所以我们不需要用这个来改变任何东西
So we didn't have to change
anything with this one.
因为我们输入了一切，我们得到了这个，一切都很好。
Because we typed everything else,
we got to this one, everything was fine.
但我看到了你的脸
But I saw all your faces.
就像狗屎一样
It was like shit, more of this.
好吧那就是整件事
Okay, so that was the entire thing.
我们要做的最后一件事是我们要去找 index.html
The one last thing that we have to do
here is we have to go to index.html and
我们得把这个从 app.js 更改为 app.tsx，对，
we have to change this from
app.js to app.tsx, right,
否则它不会指向正确的文件。
cuz otherwise it wouldn't be
pointing at the right file.
现在希望你说 npm 跑了
And now hopefully if you say npm run dev.
> > Brian Holt: 一切都应该从盒子里走出来。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Everything should
just work out of the box.
你可以看到它都来自 TypeScript。
So you can see it's all
coming from TypeScript.
> > Brian Holt: 在 10 秒内构建，我们将研究项目。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Built in ten seconds,
we'll go look at the project.
发现它还在建造，一切仍然有效。
And notice that it still builds and
everything still works.
问题 ?
Question?
>> 扬声器 2: 因此，在界面上，我在一些项目中看到了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So, on the interfaces,
I've seen in some of the projects that I'm
正在处理，它们将接口用作它们导入的单独文件。
working on, they use the interfaces
as a separate file that they import.
我注意到你把他们放在档案里了
And I noticed you put
them right into the file.
是否存在首选项，将其作为单独的接口文件，或者
Is there a preference, there's having
it in as a separate interface file, or
把它放进你用的组件里吗
just putting it in the component
that you're using it in?
>> Brian Holt: 这是一个很好的问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That's a good question.
我觉得球队会有很大的变化
I think it's gonna vary
a lot team by team.
尤其是道具和道具
For, specifically, for props and
你应该把它们放在同一个文件里
state, you should definitely
put them in the same file.
我不觉得这很有争议
And I don't feel like that's
super controversial to say,
因为它就像是那个组件的文件
because it's like documentation
of that component.
把它分开是没道理的
It wouldn't make sense to separate it.
例如，我们在此应用中使用了我们的动物和照片类型。
But for example, we used our animal and
photo type everywhere in this application.
如果不是在图书馆里定义的
Now, if that wasn't defined in a library,
我将有一个单独的接口文件来定义这些文件。
I would have a separate interface
file that would define those ones.
所以我想这就是我选择的路线。
So I guess that's kind of
the line I would choose.
如果它在一个文件中使用，那么在文件中仅定义它。
If it's used in one file,
just define it in the file.
如果它被用在一堆文件里
If it's used in a bunch of files,
把它分成另一个类型的定义
maybe split it out into
a different type definition.
>> 扬声器 2: 以我所见的方式，他们将有一个目录用于
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Cuz the way I've seen
it is they'll have a directory for
该组件和该目录组件中的
that component and
in that directory component,
您有组件，然后是 prop， iprop 和 istate 接口。
you have the component, and then the prop,
the iprop and the istate interfaces.
他们就在那儿
And they're just used there.
> > Brian Holt: 是的，这看起来很简单，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, and that seems sane,
在我工作的一个项目中，我不会感到不安。
I wouldn't be upset to see that
in a project that I worked in.
我很高兴我喜欢在一个文件里尽可能多的东西
I'm a little bit lazier that I like things
to be in one file, as much as possible.
但这是一个完全有效的选择
But that's a perfectly
valid choice to make.
我不认为有一个，你必须这样做，那种事。
I don't think there's a, you must do
it this way, kind of thing about that.
这能回答你的问题吗
Does that answer your question?
> > 演讲者 2: 是的，我想知道是否有原因，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah,
I just was wondering if there's a reason,
cutz 我更喜欢你的，不然你会打开另一个文件，你是
cuz I prefer it all in one, cuz otherwise
you kind of open up another file, you're
在寻找它的同时，你也可以看到它的存在。
looking for it, and as opposed to having
it just right all there, you can see.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，有些人只是遵守他们的标准
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, some people just
adhere to the standards that they
觉得应该是吧
feel like they should, right?
对很多人来说都是分开的
Cuz a lot of people will just separate,
他们不认为定义和代码属于同一个文件
they don't think that definitions and
code belong in the same files.
我看不出原因是吧
And I can't see why not, right?
但如果你在很多回购协议或者很多档案上
But again if you're sharing that across
a lot of repos, or a lot of files,
那就有道理了
then it does make sense.
你会从多个地方进口的对吧
Cuz you're gonna be importing it from
multiple different places, right?
这就是我的意见，但这不是意见。
So that's my opinion, but
it's not the opinion.
这只是个很好的意见
It's just a really good opinion.
很酷的问题
Cool, good question.
还有一件事我要给你看
One more thing I want to show you
before we totally wrap this up.
所以现在我们都在用我们的编辑做一切
So right now, we've just been
doing everything using our editor.
但我想让你进你的包里
But I want you to go into your
package.json, not package-lock,
package.json。
package.json.
我们再把一个东西放在这里，叫打字号，打字号。
And we're going to put one more thing
in here called typecheck, typecheck.
我们只会说 tsc -- noEmit ，就像这样。
And we're just gonna say tsc --noEmit,
like that.
这件事你可以在你的线人或
And what this is gonna do, this is
something you could run in your CI or
你可以先在当地跑出来
you could run it locally before
you commit or something like that.
因此，现在我可以说我的项目 npm 运行 typececheck。
And so now I can say my
project npm run typecheck.
所以也许你的同事在用病毒之类的东西
So that maybe your colleagues are using
vim or something like that and
他们不使用 Visual Studio 代码
they're not using Visual Studio Code.
他们可以在他们承诺要把所有东西都编译之前
They could run this before they commit to
just to make sure that everything compiles
正确。
correctly.
所以这里什么都没发生所以一切都过去了对吧
And so nothing happened here, so
it means everything passed, right?
但如果这里有问题他们就会出现
But if there were problems
here they would show up.
>> Brian Holt: 好，任何有关 TypeScript的问题吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
any questions about TypeScript?
>> Brian Holt: 是否要再次执行该操作 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Do you want to do it again?
>> Brian Holt: 我是一个大型的 TypeScript 风扇。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm a big TypeScript fan.
我认为在法律上我是有责任的
I think legally I'm obligated to be.
但是我在加入 LinkedIn 之前已经很喜欢了
But also I already liked it
before I joined LinkedIn or
在我加入微软之前
before I joined Microsoft.
我在这里的道德观是我要去
My kind of ethos in here
is that I'm going to,
如果我要做个小项目
if I'm just gonna make
a really small project,
我要用 JavaScript 把它写好然后继续
I'm gonna just write it in JavaScript and
get it done and just move on.
但是如果我写的任何项目我想保留的时间长于
But if I write any sort of project that
I intend on maintaining longer than
就像一周我要在 TypeScript里写
like a week,
I'm gonna write it in TypeScript.
因为我想最终你会获得长期收益
Because I think ultimately you're
gonna get longer term gains.
但权衡你的交易是短期交易
But the tradeoff what you're making
is you're trading off short-term
生产力来提高长期生产力，对吧 ?
productivity for
long-term productivity, right?
写的时间更长。
This takes longer to write.
毫无疑问，打打 " TypeScript" 需要更长时间。
Undoubtedly, it takes
longer to fight TypeScript.
你看到我和编译器打了好几次
You saw me fight
the compiler several times,
啊，对，这个挺甜的，对吧 ?
right, and this was pretty tame, right?
这里可以有一些检修孔让你能去很远的路
There can be some Route holes so
that you just go super far down,
那感觉毫无意义
that feel pointless.
但最终它迫使你思考自己的代码
But in the end,
it forces you to think through your code,
因为你得想，好吧，这从这里的一个串，变成了一个数字，
because you have to think, okay, this goes
from a string here, becomes a number here,
在这里变成了一个物体
goes into an object here.
比如，它迫使你思考这些事情，最终得到更好的编码。
Like, it forces you to think through these
things and you end up with better code.
你会得到额外的保证你的密码不会崩溃的
And you end up with additional assurances
that your code's not gonna crash.
所以如果有人开始对你大喊大叫，每个项目都应该使用 TypeScript ，比如
So if anyone starts yelling at you,
every project should use TypeScript, like,
连 " TypeScript " 小组都不认为是吧
not even the TypeScript team thinks that,
right?
因此，并非所有事情都需要使用 TypeScript。
So not everything needs to use TypeScript.
它有它的地方
It has its place.
但在我看来，每个大工程都应该考虑採用。
But in my opinion, every big project
should really consider adopting it.